Sarah: Hello?
Jake: Sarah?
Sarah: Hi, Jake.
Jake: Hi. Great to hear your voice!
How are things?
Sarah: Oh fine, fine.
When did you arrive in the UK?
Jake: Last night.
Sarah: And how was the journey?
Jake: Not great.
The flight was delayed for three hours.
Sarah: Oh, poor thing.
Could you do some work while you were waiting?
Jake: No, I couldn’t because there was this American guy called Alex
who was sitting next to me at the airport, and he kept talking to me.
Sarah: Oh dear.
Never mind, you’re here now.
Jake: So, when can we meet?
Sarah: I’m afraid I’m really busy this week.
The only possible day for me is Tuesday.
I’m going to London from Wednesday to Friday…
Jake: Tuesday. Let me look at my calendar.
Sarah: Wow, Jake, you put things in your calendar!
You’re much more organized than when we were going out.
Jake: Well, I’m better than I was.
Although I nearly lost my phone at the airport yesterday!
OK, Tuesday.
I’m not free in the evening.
I’m having dinner with Mark Taylor, my old professor.
Do you remember him?
It’s at seven thirty.
I can’t change that.
How about lunch?
Sarah: It depends on the time.
A late lunch would be OK, around one forty-five?
Jake: The problem is I’m giving my talk at two.
And I’m having a breakfast meeting at eight fifteen with some colleagues.
Sarah: Well, morning coffee?
Or tea in the afternoon, then?
What are you doing then?
Jake: Let’s see…
I’m going to a talk about climate change at four o clock,
so I think maybe morning coffee is best.
And then we can try to arrange another time.
Sarah: OK. There’s a nice new coffee bar in the high street called Espresso.
Meet there at eleven?
Jake: Perfect.
I’m really looking forward to it!
Sarah: Me too.
Bye.